[
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f0e",
      "correctAnswer": "Alexander Pushkin",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Nikolai Gogol",
        "Leo Tolstoy",
        "Henryk Sienkiewicz"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'Eugene Onegin'?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "6250069e0d86c8f685d80ef0",
      "correctAnswer": "Shaped pasta",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Soup pasta",
        "Stuffed pasta",
        "Ribbon pasta"
      ],
      "question": "What type of pasta is farfalle?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "italy",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950a74",
      "correctAnswer": "Norway",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Estonia",
        "Latvia",
        "Lithuania"
      ],
      "question": "Which of these countries borders Finland?",
      "tags": [
        "geography"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Society & Culture",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950135",
      "correctAnswer": "Minos",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Atticus",
        "Icarus",
        "Perseus"
      ],
      "question": "In Greek mythology, who hired Daedalus to construct the labyrinth?",
      "tags": [
        "society_and_culture"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95003b",
      "correctAnswer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Michael Jordan",
        "Yao Ming",
        "Kobe Bryant"
      ],
      "question": "Who was the NBA's most valuable player in 1976, 1977 and 1980?",
      "tags": [
        "sport",
        "basketball"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "id": "6237425acb85f7ce9e949dc4",
      "correctAnswer": "Mogadishu",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Tashkent",
        "Dushanbe",
        "Majuro"
      ],
      "question": "What is the capital city of Somalia?",
      "tags": [
        "geography"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950181",
      "correctAnswer": "James Whistler",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Andy Warhol",
        "Grant Wood",
        "Eddie Harold"
      ],
      "question": "Which american artist is known for a portrait of his mother?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "id": "6243348ccfaae40c1296144e",
      "correctAnswer": "A Joey",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "A Maggot",
        "A Piglet",
        "A Poult"
      ],
      "question": "A young kangaroo is known as what?",
      "tags": [
        "science"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "id": "62433440cfaae40c12961430",
      "correctAnswer": "A Buck",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "A Ram",
        "A Billy",
        "A Boar"
      ],
      "question": "What is a male hamster known as?",
      "tags": [
        "science"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Music",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d88",
      "correctAnswer": "Dream Theater",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Jars of Clay",
        "Three 6 Mafia",
        "The Velvet Underground"
      ],
      "question": "Which band includes 'Mike Portnoy'?",
      "tags": [
        "music"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Music",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d7a",
      "correctAnswer": "Judas Priest",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Arctic Monkeys",
        "Feeder",
        "Bring Me the Horizon"
      ],
      "question": "Which band includes 'Glenn Tipton'?",
      "tags": [
        "music"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e4b",
      "correctAnswer": "Christopher Tolkien",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Neil Gaiman",
        "J. R. R. Tolkien",
        "J. K. Rowling"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'The War of the Jewels'?",
      "tags": [
        "literature",
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Society & Culture",
      "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd3d",
      "correctAnswer": "Swahili",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Yoruba",
        "Hindi",
        "Latin"
      ],
      "question": "\"Hakuna Matata\" is a phrase from which language?",
      "tags": [
        "language",
        "society_and_culture"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "id": "6237412ccb85f7ce9e949d4a",
      "correctAnswer": "Vaduz",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Naypyidaw",
        "Vilnius",
        "Muscat"
      ],
      "question": "What is the capital city of Liechtenstein?",
      "tags": [
        "capital_cities",
        "europe"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "id": "622a1c3f7cc59eab6f9523a6",
      "correctAnswer": "Laxative",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Analgesic",
        "Anti inflammatory",
        "Suppository"
      ],
      "question": "What is the word for a medicine that hastens the emptying of the bowels?",
      "tags": [
        "medicine",
        "words",
        "science"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f8f",
      "correctAnswer": "William Shakespeare",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Arthur C. Clarke",
        "Isaac Newton",
        "Enid Blyton"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'As You Like It'?",
      "tags": [
        "theater",
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Music",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d84",
      "correctAnswer": "Kiss",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Swans",
        "The Pussycat Dolls",
        "Three 6 Mafia"
      ],
      "question": "Which band includes 'Ace Frehley'?",
      "tags": [
        "music"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502af",
      "correctAnswer": "Melon ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Cucumber",
        "Peach",
        "Pineapple"
      ],
      "question": "What Kind Of Fruit Is A Canteloupe?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502bc",
      "correctAnswer": "Pasta ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Chicken",
        "Cheese",
        "Bread"
      ],
      "question": "What Is Ravioli? ",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "general_knowledge",
        "words",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "id": "62602d254b176d54800e3c82",
      "correctAnswer": "China",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Mongolia",
        "India",
        "Australia"
      ],
      "question": "Where would you find the city of Beijing?",
      "tags": [
        "cities",
        "general_knowledge",
        "geography"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    }
  ]